Guide to the Wilbur Richard Knorr Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Papers, Accession ARCH-1994-048
  - teaching - GREEK 155 Plato 1992 -1993 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Knorr "Archimedes' Computation of Square Roots" 11/1976 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Neuenschwander translation 1980 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - St. Johns "Aristotle and Proportions" 1980 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Knorr "Aristotle, Zeno, Eudoxus" (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Knorr "The Role of Tradition… " 3/1982 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Knorr "Applied Sciences in Antiquity" Austin 4/1981 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - teaching - Alexandria UC Extension (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - teaching - Archimedes lectures (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - teaching - Renaissance Science Santa Clara 1982 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Conference of History of Mathematics 11/1989 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Nordby Ancient Applied Science (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Clagett festschrift 1986 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Knorr "Archimedes and Tradition" Maurolico 6/1979 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Knorr "Archimedes' Dimension of the Circle" 1981 -1986 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - miscellaneous correspondence and reprints 1991 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Szabo review (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - teaching - curves/optics lectures 1990 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Knorr "Greek Science in Islam" 1991 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Knorr "Commentators… "; "Grosseteste… " (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Knorr "Geoemtric Mechanics… "; "Geometric Optics… "; "Falsigraphus… " (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Think magazine material 1991 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - teaching - lecture notebooks Democritus 1974 -1977 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - teaching - lecture notebooks 1982 -1983 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - teaching - lecture notebooks Archimedes #4 10/1977 -3/1978 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - teaching - CSP HIS 06 course pack Vol.1 1993 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - manuscript - photographs (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - NEH grant application 1996 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Knorr "The Wrong Text… " reprint (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Knorr "The Wrong Text… " AMS 1995; Arizona 1996 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Knorr "Quadrans… " final (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Murdoch festschrift (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Knorr "Latin Sources… " for revision (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Knorr "The Wrong Text… " proofs, reprint, correspondence 3/1995 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Knorr "The Wrong Text… " notes, transparencies 3/1996 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - notebook 7/1995 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Damerov referee 2/1995 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Rota "The Alternative Universe" 3/1994 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Knorr "The Wrong Text… " Hamilton graphics for geometric figures (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - miscellaneous correspondence 1995 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - miscellaneous articles, notes, papers (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - regular solids 1995 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - proportions Mexico 1990, Trinity 1994 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous articles (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Zeuthen Hieberg Symposium Copenhagen 1994 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Heiberg notes (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Knorr "The Wrong Text… " transparencies (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - miscellaneous notes, transparencies, correspondence 1993 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - miscellaneous reprints, notes 1992 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - NEH grant application 1996 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - student honors thesis 6/1984 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - teaching - HIST 140 (History of Math to 1650) lectures, transparencies (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - teaching - HIST 140 handouts (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - teaching - HIST 140 course pack 1989 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - teaching - HIST 140 student work, sources, etc. 1993 -1994 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - teaching - HIST 140 1992 -1993 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - teaching - HIST 140 student work, sources, etc. 1992 -1993 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - teaching - HIST 140 handouts, sources, etc. (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - teaching - HIST 140 student work, sources, etc. 1990 -1991 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - teaching - HIST 140 student work, sources, etc. 1989 -1990 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - teaching - HIST 140 Medieval sources 1988 -1990 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - teaching - HIST 140 student work, sources, etc. 1988 -1989 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - teaching - HIST 140 evaluations 1987 -1993 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - teaching - HIST 140 notes 1987 -1988 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - teaching - HIST 140 student work, sources, etc. 1986 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - teaching - HIST 140 student work, sources, etc. 1984 -1985 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - teaching - lecture notebooks HIS 06 1993 -1994 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - teaching - lecture notebooks miscellaneous 2/1980; 10/1978 -2/1979; 2 -5/1979 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - 5 -10/1979; 10/1979; 12/1979; 10/1983; 5/1985 -6/1986
  - teaching - lecture notebooks curves problems 1977 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - teaching - lecture notebooks Archimedes #2 1 -3/1977; #3 3/1977 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - #5 3 -7/1978; #6 6/1978
  - teaching - HIST 140 student work, sources, etc. 1984 -1985 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - teaching - HIST 140 student work, sources, etc. 1983 -1984 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - teaching - HIST 140 student work 1983 -1989 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - teaching - HIST 140 math sources (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - teaching - HIST 138A reserve readings 1982 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - teaching - HIST 138C evaluations 1984 -1995 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - teaching - HUM 193 evaluations 1989 -1990 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - teaching - GREEK 101 1994 -1995 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - teaching - GREEK 103 1993 -1994 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - manuscript - miscellaneous photocopies from microfilm (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - manuscript microfilm--Seldon Supra 78 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - manuscript microfilm--Seldon Supra 2b (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - manuscript microfilm-- Marsh 621 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - manuscript microfilm--Marsh 373 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - manuscript microfilm--Canon Misc. 161 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - manuscript microfilm--Bodl. 299 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - manuscript microfilm--Bodl. 507 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - manuscript microfilm--Hunt 16, 561 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - manuscript microfilm--Hunt 435 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - manuscript microfilm--Bodl. 464 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - manuscript microfilm--Laud Misc. 644 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - manuscript microfilm--Ashmole 1522 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - manuscript microfilm--Bodl. Auct Fb23 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - manuscript microfilm--Digby 176 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - manuscript microfilm--Digby 40 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - manuscript microfilm--New CollD166 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - manuscript microfilm--Thurston 11 (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - manuscript microfilm--Lyell 89 (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - manuscript microfilm--Tanner 192 (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - manuscript microfilm--Bodley 464 (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - manuscript microfilm--Digby 76 (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - manuscript microfilm--Ashmole 341 (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - manuscript microfilm--Mus 223 (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - manuscript microfilm--Saville 21 (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - manuscript microfilm--Rawl C117 (Box 43, Folder 25)
  - manuscript microfilm--Herton 280 (Box 43, Folder 26)
  - manuscript microfilm--Bodley b79 (Box 43, Folder 27)
  - manuscript microfilm--Corpus Christi 41 (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - manuscript microfilm--Corpus Christi 221 (Box 43, Folder 29)
  - manuscript microfilm--Corpus Christi 248 (Box 43, Folder 30)
  - manuscript microfilm--Mont. 323 (Box 43, Folder 31)
  - manuscript microfilm--Colmar 414 (Box 43, Folder 32)
  - manuscript microfilm--NAL 1242 (Box 43, Folder 33)
  - manuscript microfilm--NAL 1893 (Box 43, Folder 34)
  - manuscript microfilm--Rennes 593 (Box 43, Folder 35)
  - manuscript microfilm--Sorbonne 595 (Box 43, Folder 36)
  - manuscript microfilm--Latin 6329 (Box 43, Folder 37)
  - manuscript microfilm--Latin 6626 (Box 43, Folder 38)
  - manuscript microfilm--Latin 7194 (Box 43, Folder 39)
  - manuscript microfilm--Latin 7195 (Box 43, Folder 40)
  - manuscript microfilm--Latin 7196 (Box 43, Folder 41)
  - manuscript microfilm--Latin 7298 (Box 43, Folder 42)
  - manuscript microfilm--Latin 7333 (Box 43, Folder 43)
  - manuscript microfilm--Latin 7413 1and2 (Box 43, Folder 44)
  - manuscript microfilm--Latin 7416B (Box 43, Folder 45)
  - manuscript microfilm--Latin 7420A (Box 43, Folder 46)
  - manuscript microfilm--Latin 7475 (Box 43, Folder 47)
  - manuscript microfilm--Latin 12323 (Box 43, Folder 48)
  - manuscript microfilm--Latin 14070 (Box 43, Folder 49)
  - manuscript microfilm--Latin 15121 (Box 43, Folder 50)
  - manuscript microfilm--Latin 15125 (Box 43, Folder 51)
  - manuscript microfilm--Latin 16210 (Box 43, Folder 52)
  - manuscript microfilm--Latin 16655 (Box 43, Folder 53)
  - manuscript microfilm--Latin 16658 (Box 43, Folder 54)
  - manuscript microfilm--Latin 7437 (Box 43, Folder 55)
  - manuscript microfilm--Latin 16709 (Box 43, Folder 56)
  - manuscript microfilm--Latin 7421 (Box 43, Folder 57)
  - manuscript microfilm--Latin 7281 (Box 43, Folder 58)
  - Knorr Catalog of Microfilms as of July 1979 (Box 43, Folder 59)
  - manuscript microfilm--Sloan 513 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - manuscript microfilm--SCH 28778, 33622, 67781, 54392; Add 54180, 17341, 26770, 27589 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - manuscript microfilm--SCH 14247, 54394, 54504; Add 16905, 30380; Har 4350 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - manuscript microfilm--SCH 65592; Roy 7F8 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - manuscript microfilm--SCH 97029, 97030/31; EG 823, 840b, 840c (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - manuscript microfilm--SCH 67824; EG 840A (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - manuscript microfilm--SCH 68087; Cotton Vesp A2 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - manuscript microfilm--SCH 54457, 54504, 54505; Harley 531, 3647, 3735 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - manuscript microfilm--SCH 68354, 44262, 99348; Royal 8A6, IIBxio; Arundel 115 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - manuscript microfilm--Royal 1C2 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - manuscript microfilm--SCH 65608, 65609, 65611, 52140; Royal 12.C9, 12.C17; EG 844 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - manuscript microfilm--CUL Add 1075 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - manuscript microfilm--CUL Ee 4.24d (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - manuscript microfilm--Trinity Dublin 444 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - manuscript microfilm--Ee 3.61 (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - manuscript microfilm--Trinity Dublin 514 (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - manuscript microfilm--Trinity R15.14, R15.16 (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - manuscript microfilm--St. Johns 97 (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - manuscript microfilm--Corpus Christi 352 (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - manuscript microfilm--Corpus Christi 347 (Box 44, Folder 20)
  - manuscript microfilm--Corpus Christi 154 (Box 44, Folder 21)
  - manuscript microfilm--CUL I.1.17, I.1.15, I.3.3, I.1.13 (Box 44, Folder 22)
  - manuscript microfilm--Lincoln I6 (Box 44, Folder 23)
  - manuscript microfilm--Beatty Dublin 3035, 4361, 4604 (Box 44, Folder 24)
  - manuscript microfilm--Ff 3.19 (Box 44, Folder 25)
  - manuscript microfilm--Garrett 99 (Box 44, Folder 26)
  - manuscript microfilm--Hunt. Ptolemy, Almagest (Box 44, Folder 27)
  - manuscript microfilm--Harvard Lat. 23 -36 (Box 44, Folder 28)
  - manuscript microfilm--Harvard TIP 441 -444 (Box 44, Folder 29)
  - manuscript microfilm--Harvard TIP 220 -234 (Box 44, Folder 30)
  - manuscript microfilm--Yale Medical Cushing 11 (Box 44, Folder 31)
  - manuscript microfilm--General 1115 (Box 44, Folder 32)
  - manuscript microfilm--Hunter 253 U.4.11 (Box 44, Folder 33)
  - manuscript microfilm--Eron Coll 160, 161 (Box 44, Folder 34)
  - manuscript microfilm--Getty Ludwig X116 (Box 44, Folder 35)
  - manuscript microfilm--Getty Ludwig X117 (Box 44, Folder 36)
  - manuscript microfilm--Canterbury Lit Ms. DS (Box 44, Folder 37)
  - manuscript microfilm--Glasgow Hunter 369 (Box 44, Folder 38)
  - manuscript microfilm--Glasgow Hunter 444 (Box 44, Folder 39)
  - manuscript microfilm--Glasgow Hunter 205 (Box 44, Folder 40)
  - manuscript microfilm--Glasgow Hunter 391 (Box 44, Folder 41)
  - manuscript microfilm--Vatican Lat. 2056, 1371 (Box 44, Folder 42)
  - manuscript microfilm--Vatican Lat. 1340 (Box 44, Folder 43)
  - manuscript microfilm--NYPL 69 (Box 44, Folder 44)
  - manuscript microfilm--Lat. 15185 (Box 44, Folder 45)
  - manuscript microfilm--Arsenal 590 (Box 44, Folder 46)
  - manuscript microfilm--Lat. 16211 (Box 44, Folder 47)
  - manuscript microfilm--Lat. 7366 (Box 44, Folder 48)
  - manuscript microfilm--Lat. 7363 (Box 44, Folder 49)
  - manuscript microfilm--Fr. 574 (Box 44, Folder 50)
  - manuscript microfilm--Latin 1023 (Box 44, Folder 51)
  - manuscript microfilm--St. Genevieve 1043 (Box 44, Folder 52)
  - manuscript microfilm--St. Genevieve 15 (Box 44, Folder 53)
  - manuscript microfilm--Pal. Lat. 1414 (Box 44, Folder 54)
  - manuscript microfilm--Venezia Lat. Z328 (Box 44, Folder 55)
  - manuscript microfilm--Erfurt CA4 357, 369 (Box 44, Folder 56)
  - manuscript microfilm--Firenze II III 26 (Box 44, Folder 57)
  - manuscript microfilm--Firenze Pal 639 (Box 44, Folder 58)
  - manuscript microfilm--Vat VRB. Lat. 1428 (Box 44, Folder 59)
  - manuscript microfilm--BN Lat. 7374 (Box 44, Folder 60)
  - manuscript microfilm--BN Lat. 11245 (Box 44, Folder 61)
  - manuscript microfilm--BN Lat. 16197 (Box 44, Folder 62)
  - manuscript microfilm--BN Lat. 8680A (Box 44, Folder 63)
  - manuscript microfilm--Venezia Lat. VIII 32 (Box 44, Folder 64)
  - manuscript microfilm--BN Lat 7373 (Box 44, Folder 65)
  - manuscript microfilm--BN Lat 7374A (Box 44, Folder 66)
  - manuscript microfilm--Paris BN 9335 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - manuscript microfilm--Vienna M562/84 Lat. 5210 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - manuscript microfilm--BM Add 9005 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - manuscript microfilm--BM Add 34018 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - manuscript microfilm--BM Add 17368 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - manuscript microfilm--Add 17810 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - manuscript microfilm--Sloane 3281 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - manuscript microfilm--Sloane 2435 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - manuscript microfilm--Burney 275 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - manuscript microfilm--Roy 15B4 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - manuscript microfilm--Harley 1/13 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - manuscript microfilm--Vienna Lat. 5203 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - manuscript microfilm--Vatican Lat. 1351, 3380 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - manuscript microfilm--Vienna Cod. Vind. 5277 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - manuscript microfilm--Vatican 1548 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - manuscript microfilm--Vatican Lat. 1268, 1261 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - manuscript microfilm--Conville/Caius 504/271 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - manuscript microfilm--Cambridge Fitzwilliam McClem 166 (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - manuscript microfilm--Cambridge Fitzwilliam CFM 11, Ms20 (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - manuscript microfilm--Cambridge Fitzwilliam 20 (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - manuscript microfilm--Balliol 257 (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - manuscript microfilm--Corpus Christi 251, 283 (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - manuscript microfilm--Bodl. F Auct. 5.28 (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - manuscript microfilm--Trinity Lat. 47 (Box 45, Folder 23)
  - manuscript microfilm--Bodl. Saville 119 (Box 45, Folder 24)
  - manuscript microfilm--Bodl. F. Auct. 3.13 (Box 45, Folder 25)
  - manuscript microfilm--Bodl. Digby 174 (Box 45, Folder 26)
  - manuscript microfilm--Bodl. Rawlinson 749 (Box 45, Folder 27)
  - manuscript microfilm--BN Paris Latin Euclid (Box 45, Folder 28)
  - manuscript microfilm--Db86 Dresden (Box 45, Folder 29)
  - manuscript microfilm--Trinity R.1430 (Box 45, Folder 30)
  - manuscript microfilm--Corpus Christi 364 (Box 45, Folder 31)
  - manuscript microfilm--Corpus Christi 66A (Box 45, Folder 32)
  - manuscript microfilm--Corpus Christi 66 (Box 45, Folder 33)
  - manuscript microfilm--Gonville 141/191 (Box 45, Folder 34)
  - manuscript microfilm--Gonville 512/543 (Box 45, Folder 35)
  - manuscript microfilm--Pembroke 278 (Box 45, Folder 36)
  - manuscript microfilm--CUL KK1.1 (Box 45, Folder 37)
  - manuscript microfilm--CUL KK 4.7 (Box 45, Folder 38)
  - manuscript microfilm--CUL MM 4.43 (Box 45, Folder 39)
  - manuscript microfilm--CUL Add 6866 (Box 45, Folder 40)
  - manuscript microfilm--CUL MM3.11 (Box 45, Folder 41)
  - manuscript microfilm--Firenze M 7236, 2272, 2275 (Box 45, Folder 42)
  - manuscript microfilm--Krakow 7750/84 (Box 45, Folder 43)
  - manuscript microfilm--Munich Bayerische Arabic and Hebrew (Box 45, Folder 44)
  - manuscript microfilm--Munich Bayerische Lat. 353 (Box 45, Folder 45)
  - manuscript microfilm--Laur. Plut 18/6; Gaddi 174 (Box 45, Folder 46)
  - manuscript microfilm--Plut. 18/1 -2 (Box 45, Folder 47)
  - manuscript microfilm--Stift. Lilienfeld 144 (Box 45, Folder 48)
  - manuscript microfilm--Bonn Univ. Bibl. (Box 45, Folder 49)
  - manuscript microfilm--Berlin Q33 (Box 45, Folder 50)
  - manuscript microfilm--Cod. Arab. LXXXI (Box 45, Folder 51)
  - manuscript microfilm--DKB GKS 1810, 40 (Box 45, Folder 52)
  - manuscript microfilm--Add. 447; NKS 275a (Box 45, Folder 53)
  - manuscript microfilm--Vatican 45725; Lat. 3114 (Box 45, Folder 54)
  - manuscript microfilm--Vatican Gr. 190/204 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - manuscript microfilm--Regin. Lat. 1191; Pal. Lat. 1410 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - manuscript microfilm--Pal. Lat. 1400 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - manuscript microfilm--Vatican 1356/3113 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - manuscript microfilm--Vatican Vulg. Lat. 1408; Lat. 3127; Regin. Lat. 1312 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - manuscript microfilm--Pal. Lat. 1149 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - manuscript microfilm--Pal. Lat. 1412, 1414, 1423; Vat. Lat. 3125 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - manuscript microfilm--Munich Bayerische 3515 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - manuscript microfilm--Munich Bayerische Gr. 427 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - manuscript microfilm--Österreichische Lat. 2315, 5311; Grace Phil., 31 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - manuscript microfilm--Österreichische 2367, 5508 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - manuscript microfilm--Österreichische Lat. 5878, 2445 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - manuscript microfilm--Darmstadt 2661 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - manuscript microfilm--Berlin Lat. Fol.610 (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - manuscript microfilm--GKS 277, 2 (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - manuscript microfilm--Uppsala Arabic 0.VET.20 (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - manuscript microfilm--Stockholm X767 (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - manuscript microfilm--Bodl. Marsh 709 (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - manuscript microfilm--Escorial 960 (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - manuscript microfilm--Naples IIIF; Madrid 5474 (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - manuscript microfilm--Escorial O.II.10 (Box 46, Folder 21)
  - manuscript microfilm--Ambrosiana Milano 75N9 (Box 46, Folder 22)
  - manuscript microfilm--Beatty 3076, 3652 (Box 46, Folder 23)
  - manuscript microfilm--Berlin 510 (Box 46, Folder 24)
  - manuscript microfilm--Oxford Arch. Seld. A.45 (Box 46, Folder 25)
  - manuscript microfilm--Madrid 8918 (Box 46, Folder 26)
  - manuscript microfilm--Clagett BM Selections (Box 46, Folder 27)
  - manuscript microfilm--Clagett BM Selections (orig.) (Box 46, Folder 28)
  - manuscript microfilm--St. Joseph's 150 (Box 46, Folder 29)
  - manuscript microfilm--Cambridge Hebrew Add. 1220 (Box 46, Folder 30)
  - manuscript microfilm--IOL 3/820 (Box 46, Folder 31)
  - manuscript microfilm--IOL Arabic Loth 1043 (Box 46, Folder 32)
  - manuscript microfilm--Milan Hebrew D114 (Box 46, Folder 33)
  - manuscript microfilm--Plimpton Or. 302 (Box 46, Folder 34)
  - manuscript microfilm--Smith Or. 287 (Box 46, Folder 35)
  - manuscript microfilm--Smith Or. 25 (Box 46, Folder 36)
  - manuscript microfilm--Clagett BM 227 -12K (Box 46, Folder 37)
  - manuscript microfilm--Berlin 2970 (Box 46, Folder 38)
  - manuscript microfilm--Cairo 40 (Box 46, Folder 39)
  - manuscript microfilm--Cairo 41 (Box 46, Folder 40)
  - manuscript microfilm--Vatican Hebrew 384 (Box 46, Folder 41)
  - manuscript microfilm--Bodl. Hunt 237 (Box 46, Folder 42)
  - manuscript microfilm--Bodl. Or. 2395; Thurston 1 (Box 46, Folder 43)
  - manuscript microfilm--Bodl. Marsh 669 (Box 46, Folder 44)
  - manuscript microfilm--Bodl. Thurston 3 (Box 46, Folder 45)
  - manuscript microfilm--Bodl. Or. 34; Marsh 667 (Box 46, Folder 46)
  - manuscript microfilm--Bodl. Thurston 3 (Box 46, Folder 47)
  - manuscript microfilm--Bodl. Hunt 96 (Box 46, Folder 48)
  - manuscript microfilm--Bodl. Hebrew d.4 (Box 46, Folder 49)
  - manuscript microfilm--Bodl. Land Or. 93 (Box 46, Folder 50)
  - manuscript microfilm--Bodl. Hunt 16 (Box 46, Folder 51)
  - manuscript microfilm--Basel OII7 (Box 46, Folder 52)
  - manuscript microfilm--Firenze CSJ V.30; I.32; V.29 (Box 46, Folder 53)
  - manuscript microfilm--Bodl. Menelaus (Box 46, Folder 54)
  - manuscript microfilm--Vatican Greek 184 (Box 46, Folder 55)
  - manuscript microfilm–ISIS box: Venezia Gr. 2.303, Gr. 2.310; Paris 2360; Pluo 28.18; Or 14; Or 168; Orient 15; Orient 26; Orient 155 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - manuscript microfilm--Bibliotheque Nationale, Paris mailer: Lat. 7286B, 7320, 7434, 16088, 16112, 16657, 17155; Arsenal 2872 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - manuscript microfilm--Bibliotheque Nationale, Paris mailer: Arabe 1129, 1216; Hebrew 1007, 1010 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - manuscript microfilm--Erfurt CA 4.188 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - manuscript microfilm--Utrecht 725 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - manuscript microfilm--Commande 1251.91 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - manuscript microfilm--Tours, bibl. Mun. 558 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - manuscript microfilm--Verdun 25 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - manuscript microfilm--Stad Brugge 52 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - manuscript microfilm--Leipzig Univ. 1469 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - manuscript microfilm--ESQR OII10 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - manuscript microfilm--Fleming J.11.10 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - manuscript microfilm--Rouen Bibl. Mun. 276, 192, 222, 389 (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - manuscript microfilm--Rouen Bibl. Mun. 762 (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - manuscript microfilm--Belgium 2910 -10 (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - manuscript microfilm--Erfurt Lat. 307 (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - manuscript microfilm--Modena 13 (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - manuscript microfilm--Prague 201 (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - manuscript microfilm–Paris Greek 2368 (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - manuscript microfilm–Paris Arabe 6151 (Box 47, Folder 20)
  - manuscript microfilm–Paris Arabe 2457 (Box 47, Folder 21)
  - manuscript microfilm--Lat.17155 (Box 47, Folder 22)
  - manuscript microfilm--BN Lat. 7286B (Box 47, Folder 23)
  - Burnett "Latin and Arabic Influences… " reprint 1997 (Box 47, Folder 24)
  - computer disks: approx. 100 5.25" floppy discs; 6 3.5" diskettes (labeled "Word Conversions of Knorr Docs - Spec Copies"); 2 other 3.5" diskettes (copies of Astrotable and Voyager) (Box 48, Folder 1)
- Electronic Files, Accession ARCH-1997-196
  - 37 5.25" floppy discs (Box 1)